Why are you pouring drinks yourself?
You shouldn't drink on an empty stomach, Dad.
What's wrong?
Why are you just drinking instead of eating?
Seung Ri.
Listen carefully to what I'm about to say.
I...
have a criminal record.
Dad.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry that I have to be the one to tell you this.
Twenty-five years ago,
I caused a car accident.
Someone died in that accident...
I know, Dad.
But, I always suspected...
that it was unavoidable.
That's right.
It was out of my control.
Because of that incident...
I was in prison for five years.
I wasn't transferred to the Europe office.
Jung Dong Pal...
He was my cellmate.
Stop.
That's enough.
- But, you already served your time. - Yes.
I used to think so.
That I had paid for my crime.
But...
I was wrong.
How could I ever truly pay for it when someone died?
And in the end, because of my sin,
you were the one who had to go through something so terrible.
- How did you find out? - Why on earth would you do that?
Why?
I'm the one who committed the crime.
Why did you have to suffer because of me?
I happened to overhear him blackmailing you.
Seeing you getting tormented by his blackmail,
I just couldn't stand by and do nothing.
That's why I stepped in.
You're just lucky that's all that happened.
If you had gotten seriously hurt...
That man,
he's not the kind of person you can handle.
What were you thinking, doing something so reckless?
I'm sorry, Dad.
I'll never make you worry like that again.
I may not have been a good father...
to you and Seung Woo,
or a respectable husband to your mother,
My family is my everything to me.
If you had gotten hurt in any way because of me,
I wouldn't be able to live.
Who do you think I have been working for all this time?
Why do you think I have come this far?
Please...
cherish yourself and take care, Seung Ri.
I will, Dad.
I promise.
From now on,
I'll truly cherish myself and take care.
I'm sorry.
Let's go around one more time.
What? But, we've already gone around three times.
I feel bad for being the only one to get a gift.
If I had known, I would've prepared a gift too.
Hey, what are you talking about?
You're the one who gave me a dreamcatcher...
for my room yesterday.
I think I'll be able to sleep soundly...
without nightmares from now on. Thanks to you, Eun Ae.
I really hope so.
It's so pretty.
What?
Why are you taking that off? It's your trademark.
- You've never taken it off before. - I know. It's my trademark.
- Give me your hand. - My hand?
Okay.
There. My trademark...
is now yours, Team Leader Ko.
This reminds me of the day we first met.
No cash in the wallet, and I'll cancel the cards,
so they're useless.
While the wallet is a designer brand,
I've had it for over ten years, so it's not worth much.
So just hand it over quietly.
Are you insane? Let go of me!
Hey, hold on...
Back then, that we would end up together like this...
I could not have imagined it at all.
Tell me about it.
It is funny how people end up together.
For some reason, I feel that wearing this...
will always bring me good luck,
and that only good things will happen.
Just like its name, Lucky Joy.
Of course. It has to.
- You should head in now. - Okay.
Knitting? In the middle of this heat wave?
- I have to start now for winter. - What are you knitting?
You will see.
Did Eun Ae and Team Leader Ko get back?
Yes, a little while ago.
Honey, have you given it some thought?
About what?
The Chairman wants to make you his daughter officially, on paper.
And it seems President Ko is getting very tense about it.
He asked me today what you are going to do.
Honestly, my feeling is that...
finding my mother is enough.
What is the point of a legal document?
But, after hearing what the Chairman said,
I am also conflicted.
When I think of my childhood,
not even knowing my real name or age,
moving from house to house, orphanage to orphanage,
when I think of my childhood moving around...
even now, as my mother's daughter,
I cannot deny that a part of me wants...
to make things official on paper.
But, when I think of President Ko and his wife,
trembling with fear that it might happen...
I know exactly how you feel.
There is no rush, so think it over carefully...
and do whatever you want most.
Wait a minute. What time is it?
- It is 10:55. Why? - That girl. I swear.
(Our Happy Days Real Estate, Grandma Pancake)
Wait a minute. Hey, wait, Eun Nim.
Seung Woo.
What was that all about?
I have been calling your name since the bus stop.
I did not hear you.
But, why are you here?
Are you Cinderella or something?
At the stroke of midnight, no, that is not it.
It is not like the clock is striking 11, either.
- Why did you rush out mid-writing? - Cinderella?
What are you talking about?
And besides, I am wearing my shoes perfectly fine.
That is not it.
Your bag.
- That is my bag. - Oh no. Sorry, Bung Woo.
Here you go.
Jo Eun Nim.
Mom.
Do you know what time it is?
Did I tell you to be home by eleven or not?
Good evening, ma'am.
Ma'am?
Well, I should be going then. Have a pleasant night.
Bung Nim.
- Good night. - Bye, Bung Woo.
Bung Woo? Bung Nim? Honestly, you two.
Get inside. Go on, hurry up and get inside. Goodness.
Get going.
Tell me. Seriously, my Bung Woo...
I mean, why do you hate Seung Woo so much?
You've been going on about "Bung Woo" and "Bung Nim."
Are those your pet names for each other?
- Are you two really dating? - Not exactly...
No, but seriously, why do you hate him so much?
I don't like the way he looks. That's why.
What? What's wrong with his looks? He's so handsome.
Haven't you heard that pretty boys are trouble?
He's probably swarming with girls, right?
No, not swarming. Maybe just one?
Either way, he's obviously the type that attracts girls.
Is it a crime to be handsome?
If that's the case, what about Team Leader Ko?
Team Leader Ko is handsome, too.
Why aren't you trying to stop Seung Ri?
Are you saying their good looks are the same?
Anyone can see Team Leader Ko has strong principles,
no matter who tries to sway him,
he looks like he'd stand his ground.
That kid from before, if someone tried to sway him,
he seems like he'd be easily swayed and unreliable.
Wow, Mom, that's ridiculous. Do you even know Bung Woo?
- Do you? - That's not all.
I don't like his job either.
No matter what, a man needs to have a stable job.
What's a webtoon artist?
How is he supposed to make a living drawing comics?
This isn't going to end.
By that logic, your daughter is a web novel writer.
Mom, it's impossible to even have a conversation with you.
What do you mean?
Do you think I'm doing this for myself?
You're going to say, "This is all for your own good,"
aren't you, Mom?
Unbelievable.
Are you feeling a bit better, Dad?
I'm fine now.
Seung Ri, let me ask you for one more favour.
Yes, tell me.
The things we talked about today,
let's take them to our graves.
Seung Woo and your mother must never find out.
Got it?
Of course. I know exactly what you mean.
Gosh.
Why on earth does she dislike me so much?
Bung Nim's mother.
I want to make a good impression.
What?
Dad.
- Seung Ri. - Hey, Seung Woo.
What are you two doing here?
Gosh, what secrets are you two whispering about?
What secrets?
- I had a date with Dad. Why? - A date?
Hold on.
Is that the smell of ribs?
Don't tell me you two just went out for ribs?
Seung Woo, I'm sorry.
I had to discuss something about work...
with your sister today. Next time, let's all go as a family.
Wait a minute. Does that mean Mom's been home alone all this time?
What?
Mom's menopause symptoms have seemed really bad lately.
- We're in big trouble. - Kids, let's go.
- Okay. - Oh, honestly.
- Hurry. - Run.
Mom, we're home.
Mom, are you sleeping?
We're here.
What do we do? I think she's really upset with us.
Honey.
Seung Ri and I were delayed talking about work,
and we ran into Seung Woo right outside.
I'm sorry. Next time, we'll be sure to go together...
Oh, come on, Mom.
(Gangsu Construction)
Are you almost done?
Everyone else went to lunch. Should we go too?
What? Oh, were you waiting for me?
You should go get some lunch. I have to go somewhere.
Where to?
The police station.
The police station? Why?
I'm going to look up some of my father's records.
It's been a long time, so I'm not sure...
- if I'll find anything. - In that case, I'll go with you.
I don't feel right about you going alone.
No, it's okay. This might take a while,
so I took a half-day off. You should get back to work, Eun Ae.
Are you sure you'll be okay on your own?
Of course. I've got this with me. I'll just pretend you're with me.
Well, shall I get going?
(Police)
(To Improve The Public's Perception Of Safety)
(Mobile Civil Complaint Counselling)
(Application For Traffic Accident Report)
(Applicant: Ko Gyeol)
(Date Of Accident: May 16, 2001)
(Location)
Excuse me.
I don't know where the accident occurred.
Can I still get the report?
- Let me check for you. - Okay.
An accident in 2001? So, 25 years ago?
Yes, that's right.
This probably wouldn't have been digitized.
I'm sorry, but we can't find it on our end.
Does that mean there's no way to find it at all?
Not necessarily.
You should try going to the station that had jurisdiction.
The station with jurisdiction?
Yes, the one that handled the accident at the time.
The files might still be there.
If it's the station that handled the accident,
I need to know where it happened, right?
Right.
(Officer Kim Jun Ho)
You don't remember the location at all?
No.
Then I'll try to run a case search...
with the information you've provided.
Yes, thank you.
- Okay, look at me, all right? - Okay.
One, two.
One, two, three.
- One, two, three. - Ma'am,
- your sense of rhythm is... - One, two, three, four, one, two.
a natural gift. If you had gone into showbiz...
instead of making pancakes,
you could've easily become a famous pop singer.
Right? If I had gone that route back in the day,
Kim Chu Ja, Jeong Hun Hui, and Hye Eun Yi,
- they would've starved. - Right.
My goodness.
- Have you been waiting long? - Oh, my.
We could have just come on our own. Why did you send a car?
We've troubled you so much, Mr. Ju.
Oh, it's no trouble at all. The Chairman is so excited...
at the thought of seeing his grandchildren...
and great-granddaughter.
- Shall we get going? - Yes.
- Ms. Park, see you at the studio. - Okay. Take care.
My, they say life is full of twists and turns.
Who would have thought Eun Hyung's family...
would have such a joyous occasion?
- Hardly an occasion. I'll be back. - Okay.
Let's go.
- Yes, let's go. - Bit Na looks so pretty.
Bit Na, have a good time at your great-grandmother's house.
- Okay, Auntie. Bye-bye. - Let's go.
- Bye-bye. - Bit Na, let's go.
Eun Hyung looks amazing in that suit.
- Right, Grandma? - Amazing in what? Speak clearly.
You know, when I was little, I used to have this fantasy.
- Yes? - That I was secretly...
the long-lost daughter of a rich family,
and my birth mother would come looking for me.
Then what about me? What am I,
the one who worked her butt off to raise you?
I'm just saying it was a fantasy I used to have.
- Anyway, Grandma. - Yes?
What's the deal with you and Yong Man, or Secretary Ju?
The deal?
What in the world are you talking about?
He's a younger friend who drops by my restaurant.
We're in the same line dancing class.
- Why? - I mean... Right.
Yes, I guess my imagination got carried away.
- What were you imagining now? - It's nothing.
Gosh. You are so bland, you must not eat enough salt.
It's a shame Eun Ae isn't here with us,
but you've raised your three children...
to be very respectable.
Oh, hardly.
They didn't all turn out exactly as I'd hoped,
but I'm satisfied that they're diligent...
and pull their own weight.
That's what's most important, of course.
- Your name is Bit Na? - Yes, Jo Bit Na.
- I missed you, Great-Grandma. - Oh, my.
- You too, Great-Grandpa. - Oh, really?
This grandpa missed my great-granddaughter...
very much too.
You're so pretty and smart too.
I heard you have a doctorate in philosophy,
but because of the times, you can't land a teaching position?
That's right.
But, even if it's not at a university,
I'm still able to fulfill my duty of teaching students,
- so I don't have major complaints. - That's the spirit.
Do you know how your mother and I first met?
Our youngest granddaughter...
- brought mother and me together. - What? I did?
That's right. The day I first found out...
you dropped out of school,
I happened to run into your grandmother...
in front of the hospital.
Oh, I see.
I'm back.
Kang Yeon Ja.
Well, look at this. The whole family's here.
Come on, say hello. This is your great-aunt.
- Hello. - Hello.
Oh, yes, nice to meet you. Welcome.
Yes, everyone, have a seat.
What? It's that lady from before.
- Grandma's friend who came over. - What?
Have you seen me before?
Yes. You came to our house and asked to see Grandma's necklace.
You were so surprised when you saw it.
What? I did? When?
- Oh, for goodness' sake. - What is she talking about?
A necklace?
Don't tell me...
When was this?
No, it's just...
It was a long time ago. It was nothing.
My, what a sharp eye you have for a little kid.
Excuse me. Father,
I bought this outfit for the living funeral.
- Would you like to see it? - No. I'll look at it later.
Okay. I made sure it is very luxurious,
befitting of a party,
and I prepared something glamorous, Father.
What? You mean all the grandkids and even the great-granddaughter?
It seems she's really going all out.
All right, I get it. I'll be home early.
Yes. Okay, bye.
Yes, come in.
(Gangsu Construction)
What brings you here?
It's about the preparations for Grandfather's funeral.
Seung Ri and I drafted a tentative program.
Please take a look.
Not you too. Is everyone okay with a funeral...
- for someone who is still alive? - You know it's Grandfather's wish.
Also, I am going to propose to Seung Ri again soon.
I am just letting you know.
What is wrong with you, seriously?
Are you trying to give your father a heart attack?
Father.
You married Mom because you truly loved her, right?
Of course.
Why do you ask?
If Grandfather had been against your marriage back then,
would you have just given up?
What? Of course not.
How could I have given up on your mother?
See? My point exactly.
You would not have given up,
- so why are you forcing me to? - No, our situations are different.
Okay, fine.
Let us say I am willing to give up on marrying you off for connections.
But...
Seo Gwon Sik and I can never be in-laws. Understand?
But, why? Why are you two on such bad terms?
There is no reason. It just cannot happen.
It is absolutely impossible.
Fine. If that is how you are going to be,
I do not need your permission.
I am not giving up on Seung Ri, no matter what. Just so you know.
Hey, you. Hey, Ko Min Ho.
That brat. Hey, you, take this. I said take this with you.
Gosh. Unbelievable.
Since the cost of purchasing land is...
the biggest portion of the project budget,
we must thoroughly vet its commercial viability.
Yes, once we have the candidate sites,
I will conduct a thorough comparative analysis.
I'll also start by compiling a list of locations...
that fit our Retirement Community's concept.
Then I will pull some more related materials...
from the archives before I head home.
- See you tomorrow. - Yes, thank you for your hard work.
Okay.
Oh, right.
What happened at the police station?
It's not easy.
The accident was so long ago that they said...
it couldn't be found in the system.
Instead, they traced it to the police station...
that had jurisdiction,
so I filed a request for the accident records there.
- Are they able to look it up there? - No.
Well, they said they would look,
but the records may have been disposed of.
I guess I will just have to wait and see.
That's really tough.
So that's why you looked so down all day.
Well, you went through a lot today. You're heading straight home, right?
How about we grab a quick dinner,
and then work on the video for Grandfather's event together?
Sure. How about we eat, take a walk to clear our heads,
- and then come back? - Yes, let's do that.
Hey, shouldn't we head home?
Yes, I guess so.
Oh, by the way, about Team Leader Ko.
Do you know anything about how he was adopted by President Ko?
What? Why do you ask?
President Ko already has his own son,
so I'm curious why he'd go out of his way...
to adopt Team Leader Ko.
They say President Ko only agreed because the Chairman told him to.
Was he the son of an acquaintance of the Chairman?
The Chairman? I am not sure.
I just heard they got him from an orphanage.
And President Ko just accepted that?
That's surprising.
I don't really know.
But, if that's what President Ko said...
I guess that must be it.
Yes, I guess so.
Let's head out.
Honey. Today, I bought outfits for your parents...
to wear at Father's living funeral, and for us too. Want to see?
They said the theme is a fun and exciting party,
so I picked out the most fabulous outfits for us.
Crystal, are you being serious right now?
What, am I the only one who thinks this is weird?
Am I the only one who can't accept this funeral?
Oh, please. Father's word is law.
We have to do as he says. What other choice is there?
No, I can't do it. Absolutely not.
Oh, please. What are you going to do if you don't?
What do you mean you're against it? I've explained everything,
so why can't you understand what I want?
I know. But, no matter how hard I try to understand and accept it...
- I just can't do it. - Unbelievable.
If you still have enough energy to hold your own funeral in advance,
why won't you consider getting more aggressive treatment?
Why are you trying to give up on your life already?
Why are you being so stubborn? Why?
It's because while I still have some energy left,
I want to say a happy goodbye to the people I love.
I'm not giving up on my life.
I just want to wrap things up comfortably and naturally...
- on my own terms. - That is giving up.
It means you've lost your will to live, doesn't it?
I know I may have been a disappointment as a son,
but I really don't want you to die, Father.
I know I've only disappointed you so far,
and I know it's late,
but from now on, I want to get my act together...
and show you I can be a good son.
I really want to show you that,
so why are you only thinking about leaving?
Ko Dae Chi.
That sentiment is more than enough for me.
Just as you've said,
you just have to live like that from now on.
Don't be greedy.
Just live with a generous heart.
If you do that,
then I will have nothing more to ask of you.
Father.
Seriously.
(Our Happy Days Real Estate, Grandma Pancake)
I've been thinking.
Even if the police station doesn't have the files anymore,
the fact that the precinct is running a search...
means a record of the case must exist.
Then at least some basic information about the accident should be left.
Based on that, there must be another way...
to find what we're looking for.
For now, we just have to wait.
Also, what about asking your grandfather?
You said your father was a valued employee of his, right?
Don't you think he might know something?
He might, but he's not well.
If he finds out I'm doing this, he'll just worry more,
so I was trying not to tell him if possible.
Don't worry too much.
I'm sure we'll find an answer if we keep looking.
- We should go in. - Okay.
Still not home yet?
I was hoping to talk about the site selection.
Father.
Hey, Team Leader Ko.
(Our Happy Days)
Oh, dear. What's wrong?
Oh my, are you all right?
We can still cancel. Okay?
There won't be a next time.
The Cheongbin Police Traffic Investigation Unit?
Have you found anything?
You need to get that look off your face.
People will think something is wrong.
I have brought you all here today...
to share a joyful and happy farewell.
Thank you for being a part of my life.
(Our Happy Days)